Barbara B. Kennelly Papers
© 2004 University of Connecticut
- Series V: Subject Files, 1978-1998
  - Subseries J: 105th Congress, 1997-1998
    - Multiple Employer Welfare Association (MEWA)'s Health Reform Bill, 1996-1998 (Box 48:, Folder 19)
    - NTU: Pension Issue, 1998 (Box 48:, Folder 20)
    - Post Office, 1998 (Box 48:, Folder 21)
    - Prostate Cancer - Zoladex, 1998 (Box 48:, Folder 22)
    - Retirement Age Hearing, 1998 (Box 48:, Folder 23)
    - Route 6, 1998 (Box 48:, Folder 24)
    - Small Business, 1998 (Box 48:, Folder 25)
    - Social Security - Archer Social Security Commission, 1998 (Box 48:, Folder 26)
    - Social Security - Kolbe / Stenholm Super Committee, 1998 (Box 48:, Folder 27)
    - SSA Commissioner Hearing, 1998 (Box 48:, Folder 28)
    - State of Union and Social Security, 1998 (Box 48:, Folder 29)
    - Transportation, 1998 (Box 48:, Folder 30)
    - UConn HC HCFA Survey, 1998 (Box 48:, Folder 31)
    - Veterans, 1998 (Box 48:, Folder 32)
  - Subseries K: Date Unknown, undated
    - Abortion Statement, undated (Box 49:, Folder 1)
    - Favorite Quotes of John F. Kennedy and Robert F. Kennedy, undated (Box 49:, Folder 2)
    - Leadership Breifing for New Members, undated (Box 49:, Folder 3)
    - Let the Word Go Forth - The Speeches, Statements, and Writings of John F. Kennedy, undated (Box 49:, Folder 4)
    - Radio America Scripts, undated (Box 49:, Folder 5)
    - Ways and Means - BBK's Future - Rostenkowski's Fall Could Mean Rise of Barbara Kennelly, undated (Box 49:, Folder 6)
- Series VI: Correspondence, undated, 1982-1998
  - Letters Originated By BBK, 1982 January - June (Box 49:, Folder 7)
  - Letters Originated By BBK, 1982 July - December (Box 49:, Folder 8)
  - USSR, 1984 (Box 49:, Folder 9)
  - Apartheid: Letter to the Editor of the Journal Inquirer, 1985 (Box 49:, Folder 10)
  - Ross Brown - Correspondence, 1985 (Box 49:, Folder 11)
  - Conn-Save - BBK Endorsement, 1985 (Box 49:, Folder 12)
  - Cosmopolitan Business and Professional Women's Club - Luncheon, 1985 (Box 49:, Folder 13)
  - Historic Rehabilitation Tax Credit - New Britain Herald Letter, 1985 (Box 49:, Folder 14)
  - Letter to the Editor of the Hartford Advocate - Tax Reform, 1985 (Box 49:, Folder 15)
  - Network - Narw-Network Event - Washington, D.C., 1985 (Box 49:, Folder 16)
  - Connecticut Federation of Democratic Women - Breakfast, 1986 (Box 49:, Folder 17)
  - NOW Vatican Demonstation - BBK Letter to National Organization for Women, 1987 (Box 49:, Folder 18)
  - 76th Division Letter to Secretary of the Army, 1989 (Box 49:, Folder 19)
  - 76th Division Letters, 1989 (Box 49:, Folder 20)
  - Environment - Norwalk Harbor Appropriations, 1989 (Box 49:, Folder 21)
  - Public Relations 1988-1989 (Box 49:, Folder 22)
  - Public Relations 1989, 1988-1989 (Box 49:, Folder 23-25)
  - Public Relations 1990/Unknown Date, 1988-1989 (Box 49:, Folder 26)
  - Letter for Guard UH-60 (Blackhawk Helicoptors), 1990 (Box 49:, Folder 27)
  - Letter for Norden on JSTAR, 1990 (Box 49:, Folder 28)
  - Letter on Facility for Connecticut Air National Guard, 1990 (Box 49:, Folder 29)
  - Letter to Cheney on Submarines, 1990 (Box 49:, Folder 30)
  - Letter to Nunn, 1990 (Box 49:, Folder 31)
  - Letter To Secretary of Defense Cheney on Program Objective Memorandum and Light Helicopter Program, 1990 (Box 49:, Folder 32)
  - Letter to Watkins for UNC/AVLIS, 1990 (Box 49:, Folder 33)
  - Letters to Other Members, 1990 (Box 49:, Folder 34)
  - BBK Letters, 1991 (Box 49:, Folder 35)
  - Connecticut Guard Letters, 1991 (Box 49:, Folder 36)
  - Letter on Base Closings, 1991 (Box 49:, Folder 37)
  - Letter to KLM President, 1991 (Box 49:, Folder 38)
  - Letters to Conver/Greenburg, 1991 (Box 49:, Folder 39)
  - Public Law 102-209 D.C. Bicentennial Month, 1991 (Box 49:, Folder 40)
  - Quicksilver Letter to Conway/Cheney, 1991 (Box 49:, Folder 41)
  - Steve Cosponsor Records 102nd Congress, 1991 (Box 49:, Folder 42)
  - Cosigned Letter File, 1992 January - June (Box 50:, Folder 1)
  - Cosigned Letter File, 1992 July - December (Box 50:, Folder 2)
  - Defense Delegation Letters and Responses, 1992 (Box 50:, Folder 3)
  - Fuel Cell Projects, 1992 (Box 50:, Folder 4)
  - Letters - McKinney Homeless Act, 1992 (Box 50:, Folder 5)
  - Letters to the Editor, 1990-1992 (Box 50:, Folder 6)
  - Urban Caucus Health Letter to Panetta, 1992 (Box 50:, Folder 7)
  - Wilkey/Checks Letter, 1992 (Box 50:, Folder 8)
  - BBK Congress Signed Letters, 1993 (Box 50:, Folder 9)
  - Connecticut Delegation Letters, 1993 (Box 50:, Folder 10)
  - Planned Parenthood - Letter on HR 796, 1993 (Box 50:, Folder 11)
  - Sikorsky/Blackhawk, 1993 (Box 50:, Folder 12)
  - Sent Letters, 1994 (Box 50:, Folder 13)
  - Signed Letters and Responses, 1994 (Box 50:, Folder 14)
  - Aetna Letters, 1995 (Box 50:, Folder 15)
  - D.O.D. Appropriations Letter, 1955 (Box 50:, Folder 16)
  - EPA Letter, 1995 (Box 50:, Folder 17)
  - Memoranda, 1995 (Box 50:, Folder 18)
  - Memoranda/Committee Letters, 1995 (Box 50:, Folder 19)
  - 104th Congress (Letters), 1995-1996 (Box 50:, Folder 20-22)
  - 105th Congress 1997-1998 (Letters) (Box 50:, Folder 23)
  - BBK's Letters, 1997 (Box 50:, Folder 24)
  - UTC and Interline Letter, 1997 (Box 50:, Folder 25)
  - Letters 1997-1998, 1997 January - June (Box 50:, Folder 26)
  - Letters 1997-1998, 1997 July - December (Box 50:, Folder 27)
  - Letters 1997-1998, 1998 January - November (Box 51:, Folder 1)
  - Signed Letters, 1997-1998 (Box 51:, Folder 2)
  - 105th Congress 1997-1998 (Letters), 1998 January - May (Box 51:, Folder 3)
  - 105th Congress 1997-1998 (Letters), 1998 June - August (Box 51:, Folder 4)
  - 105th Congress 1997-1998 (Letters), 1998 September - December (Box 51:, Folder 5)
  - BBK's Letters, 1998 (Box 51:, Folder 6-7)
  - Air Traffic Controlers, 1998 (Box 51:, Folder 8)
  - Ida Nudel - Letter to BBK, undated (Box 51:, Folder 9)
- Series VII: Writings, undated, 1982-1994
    - Capitol Hill Women's Political Cacus Newsletter - BBK Column, 1982 (Box 51:, Folder 10)
    - Media - Editorials, 1982 (Box 51:, Folder 11)
    - Op/Ed - Election of BBK, 1982 (Box 51:, Folder 12)
    - Child Support Enforcement / Column, 1983 (Box 51:, Folder 13)
    - Tandem Trucks Ban - Column, 1983 (Box 51:, Folder 14)
    - Child Support - Judy Mann Column, 1984 (Box 51:, Folder 15)
    - Child Support - Op Ed, 1984 (Box 51:, Folder 16)
    - Medicare - Column, 1984 (Box 51:, Folder 17)
    - Employee Benefits - New England Council Article, 1985 (Box 51:, Folder 18)
    - Hartford Woman - "Comparable Worth" by BBK, 1985 (Box 51:, Folder 19)
    - National Business Woman - "Tax Reform: The Challenge of the Eighties." - Oct/Nov 1985 Issue (Box 51:, Folder 20)
    - Op/Ed - "Simplifying Taxes: No Simple Task", 1985 (Box 51:, Folder 21)
    - Op/Ed - Hartford Courant - "Pass Tax Reform Now", 1985 (Box 51:, Folder 22)
    - Pension Actuary - Article on VIP Bill, 1985 (Box 51:, Folder 23)
    - Connecticut Coalition on Aging - Article, 1986 (Box 51:, Folder 24)
    - Risk Pool - Op-Ed, 1986 (Box 51:, Folder 25)
    - St. Mary's College - The Observer - BBK article Opposing Aid to Contras, 1986 (Box 51:, Folder 26)
    - Connecticut Coalition on Aging - Article - Preventing Cancer in Older Women, 1989 (Box 51:, Folder 27)
    - National Business Women - Article on Pensions, 1989 (Box 51:, Folder 28)
    - OP/ED - Cutting Taxes: Not Just For the Rich", 1990 (Box 51:, Folder 29)
    - OP/ED - Payment of Death Benefits, 1990 (Box 51:, Folder 30)
    - OP/ED - Hartford: "The Federal Government Must Help", 1991 (Box 51:, Folder 31)
    - Newsletters, 1982-1992 (Box 51:, Folder 32)
    - BBK OP/Eds, 1993 (Box 51:, Folder 33)
    - NannyGate Op-Ed, 1994 (Box 51:, Folder 34)
    - APPWP - Guest Editorial - Pension Reform, unknown (Box 51:, Folder 35)
    - Article - The Nuclear Freeze: Where From Here? - Draft for Radcliffe Quarterly, unknown (Box 51:, Folder 36)
    - Budget Cuts - Connecticut Elder, unknown (Box 51:, Folder 37)
    - CT Woman Magazine - Legislative Priorities, unknown (Box 51:, Folder 38)
    - Tax Reform - Op/Ed - USA Today, unknown (Box 51:, Folder 39)
- Series VIII: Bound Reports, 1983-1995
    - "Tax Investment of Life Insurance" Hearings before Ways and Means Sub-committee, 1983 (Box 51:, Folder 40)
    - Griffin Line Corridor - Major Investment Study By: Greater Hartford Transit District, 1995 (Box 51:, Folder 51)
- Series IX: Press Clips, 1982-1998
    - Magazine Clips - BBK Elected, 1982 (Box 52:, Folder 1)
    - Press Clips - BBK Swearing In, 1982 (Box 52:, Folder 2)
    - Press Clips - CT Elections, 1982 (Box 52:, Folder 3)
    - Press Clips - District (Mojo), 1982 (Box 52:, Folder 4)
    - Press Clips - Election, 1982 (Box 52:, Folder 5)
    - Press Clips - Environment: Acid Rain, 1982 (Box 52:, Folder 6)
    - Press Clips - Environment: Hazardous Waste, 1982 (Box 52:, Folder 7)
    - Press Clips - Federal Trade Commission, 1982 (Box 52:, Folder 8)
    - Press Clips - Insurance, 1982 (Box 52:, Folder 9)
    - Press Clips - News Articles, 1982 (Box 52:, Folder 10)
    - Press Clips - Taxes: Tuition Tax Credit, 1982 (Box 52:, Folder 11)
    - Press Clips 1982-1983 (1 of 3) (Box 52:, Folder 12)
    - Press Clips 1982-1983 (2 of 3) (Box 52:, Folder 13)
    - Press Clips 1982-1983 (3 of 3) (Box 52:, Folder 14)
    - Press Clips - Mar 1984 (Box 52:, Folder 15)
    - Press Clips - Apr 1984 (Box 52:, Folder 16)
    - Press Clips - May 1984 (Box 52:, Folder 17)
    - Press Clips - Jun 1984 (Box 52:, Folder 18)
    - Press Clips - Jul 1984 (Box 52:, Folder 19)
    - Press Clips - Aug 1984 (Box 52:, Folder 20)
    - Press Clip - Connecticut Caucus of Black Women, 1985 (Box 52:, Folder 21)
    - Press Clips - 1985 (1 of 2) (Box 52:, Folder 22)
    - Press Clips - 1985 (2 of 2) (Box 52:, Folder 23)
    - Press Clips - September 1985 (1 of 2) (Box 52:, Folder 24)
    - Press Clips - September 1985 (2 of 2) (Box 52:, Folder 25)
    - Press Clips - May 1986 (Box 52:, Folder 26)
    - Press Clips - Jun 1986 (Box 52:, Folder 27)
    - Press Clips - Jul 1986 (Box 52:, Folder 28)
    - Press Clips - Aug 1986 (Box 52:, Folder 29)
    - Press Clips - Sep 1986 (Box 52:, Folder 30)
    - Press Clips - Oct 1986 (Box 52:, Folder 31)
    - Press Clips - Nov 1986 (Box 52:, Folder 32)
    - Press Clips - Dec 1986 (Box 52:, Folder 33)
    - Rehab Credit - Press Articles, 1986 (Box 52:, Folder 34)
    - Press Clips - Jan 1987 (Box 53:, Folder 1)
    - Press Clips - Feb 1987 (Box 53:, Folder 2)
    - Press Clips - Mar 1987 (Box 53:, Folder 3)
    - Press Clips - Apr 1987 (Box 53:, Folder 4)
    - Press Clips - May 1987 (Box 53:, Folder 5)
    - Press Clips - Jun 1987 (Box 53:, Folder 6)
    - Press Clips - Jul 1987 (Box 53:, Folder 7)
    - Press Clips - Aug 1987 (Box 53:, Folder 8)
    - Press Clips - Colt - Workers Strike, 1987 (Box 53:, Folder 9)
    - Press Clips - 1988 (1 of 2) (Box 53:, Folder 10)
    - Press Clips - 1988 (2 of 2) (Box 53:, Folder 11)
    - Press Clips - October 1988 (Box 53:, Folder 12)
    - Press Clip - 16 Youth Win Appointment to U.S. Service Academies, 1988 (Box 53:, Folder 13)
    - Press Clips - 1989 (Box 53:, Folder 14)
    - Press Clips - February 1989 (Box 53:, Folder 15)
    - Press Clips - September 1989 (Box 53:, Folder 16)
    - Press Clips - Jan, Feb, Mar 1992 (Box 53:, Folder 17)
    - Press Clips - Apr, May 1992 (Box 53:, Folder 18)
    - Press Clips - Jun, Jul, Aug 1992 (Box 53:, Folder 19)
    - Press Clips - September 1992 (Box 53:, Folder 20)
    - Press Clips - Oct, Nov, Dec 1992 (Box 53:, Folder 21)
    - Press Clips - January 1993 (Box 53:, Folder 22)
    - Press Clips - February 1993 (Box 53:, Folder 23)
    - Press Clips - March 1993 (Box 53:, Folder 24)
    - Press Clips - April 1993 (Box 53:, Folder 25)
    - Press Clips - May 1993 (Box 53:, Folder 26)
    - Press Clips - June 1993 (Box 53:, Folder 27)
    - Press Clips - Sept 1993 (Box 53:, Folder 28)
    - Press Clips - Oct 1993 (Box 53:, Folder 29)
    - Press Clips - Nov 1993 (Box 53:, Folder 30)
    - Press Clips - Dec 1993 (Box 53:, Folder 31)
    - Press Clips - Elections 1993 Mayoral (Box 53:, Folder 32)
    - Press Clips - Hong Kong / PRC, 1993 (Box 53:, Folder 33)
    - Press Clips - Trade - NAFTA, 1993 (Box 53:, Folder 34)
    - Press Clippings, 1993 (Box 53:, Folder 35)
    - Press Clips - Jan 1994 (Box 54:, Folder 1)
    - Press Clips - Feb 1994 (Box 54:, Folder 2)
    - Press Clips - Mar 1994 (Box 54:, Folder 3)
    - Press Clips - Apr 1994 (Box 54:, Folder 4)
    - Press Clips - May 1994 (Box 54:, Folder 5)
    - Press Clips - Jun 1994 (Box 54:, Folder 6)
    - Press Clips - Jul 1994 (Box 54:, Folder 7)
    - Press Clips - Aug 1994 (Box 54:, Folder 8)
    - Press Clips - Sep 1994 (Box 54:, Folder 9)
    - Press Clips - Oct 1994 (Box 54:, Folder 10)
    - Press Clips - Nov 1994 (Box 54:, Folder 11)
    - Press Clips - Dec 1994 (Box 54:, Folder 12)
    - Press Clips - Administration - Whitewater, 1994 (Box 54:, Folder 13)
    - Press Clips - Congress - Abortion 1994 (Box 54:, Folder 14)
    - Press Clips - Congress - Budget 1994 (Box 54:, Folder 15)
    - Press Clips - Congress - Campaign Finance 1994 (Box 54:, Folder 16)
    - Press Clips - Congress - Crime 1994 (Box 54:, Folder 17)
    - Press Clips - Congress - Foreign Affairs 1994 (Box 54:, Folder 18)
    - Press Clips - Congress - Rostenkowski, 1994 (Box 54:, Folder 19)
    - Press Clips - Editorials - Courant 1994 (Box 54:, Folder 20)
    - Press Clips - Editorials J-I, 1994 (Box 54:, Folder 21)
    - Press Clips - Elections - 1st District, 1994 (Box 54:, Folder 22)
    - Press Clips - Elections - 2nd District, 1994 (Box 54:, Folder 23)
    - Press Clips - Elections - 3rd District, 1994 (Box 54:, Folder 24)
    - Press Clips - Elections - 4th District, 1994 (Box 54:, Folder 25)
    - Press Clips - Elections - 5th District, 1994 (Box 54:, Folder 26)
    - Press Clips - Elections - 6th District, 1994 (Box 54:, Folder 27)
    - Press Clips - Elections - Endorsements, 1994 (Box 54:, Folder 28)
    - Press Clips - Elections - General Results, 1994 (Box 54:, Folder 29)
    - Press Clips - Elections - Gubernatorial (1 of 2), 1994 (Box 54:, Folder 30)
    - Press Clips - Elections - Gubernatorial (2 of 2), 1994 (Box 54:, Folder 31)
    - Press Clips - Elections - Other, 1994 (Box 54:, Folder 32)
    - Press Clips - Elections - Primary Results, 1994 (Box 54:, Folder 33)
    - Press Clips - Elections - Senate, 1994 (Box 54:, Folder 34)
    - Press Clips - General Assembly, 1994 (Box 54:, Folder 35)
    - Press Clips - Governor Weicker, 1994 (Box 54:, Folder 36)
    - Press Clips - Health - Long Term Care, 1994 (Box 55:, Folder 1)
    - Press Clips - Health Care Reform - Abortion, 1994 (Box 55:, Folder 2)
    - Press Clips - Health Care Reform - Clinton, 1994 (Box 55:, Folder 3)
    - Press Clips - Health Care Reform - Connecticut, 1994 (Box 55:, Folder 4)
    - Press Clips - Health Care Reform - Costs, 1994 (Box 55:, Folder 5)
    - Press Clips - Health Care Reform - House Committees, 1994 (Box 55:, Folder 6)
    - Press Clips - Health Care Reform - House Floor, 1994 (Box 55:, Folder 7)
    - Press Clips - Health Care Reform - Insurance, 1994 (Box 55:, Folder 8)
    - Press Clips - Health Care Reform - Jim Cooper, 1994 (Box 55:, Folder 9)
    - Press Clips - Health Care Reform - Leaders, 1994 (Box 55:, Folder 10)
    - Press Clips - Health Care Reform - Medicaid, 1994 (Box 55:, Folder 11)
    - Press Clips - Health Care Reform - Senate Committees, 1994 (Box 55:, Folder 12)
    - Press Clips - Health Care Reform - Senate Floor, 1994 (Box 55:, Folder 13)
    - Press Clips - John Baily, 1994-1995 (Box 55:, Folder 14)
    - Press Clips - Jan 1995 (Box 55:, Folder 15)
    - Press Clips - Feb 1995 (Box 55:, Folder 16)
    - Press Clips - Mar 1995 (Box 55:, Folder 17)
    - Press Clips - Apr 1995 (Box 55:, Folder 18)
    - Press Clips - May 1995 (Box 55:, Folder 19)
    - Press Clips - Jun 1995 (Box 55:, Folder 20)
    - Press Clips - Jul 1995 (Box 55:, Folder 21)
    - Press Clips - Aug 1995 (Box 55:, Folder 22)
    - Press Clips - Sep 1995 (Box 55:, Folder 23)
    - Press Clips - Oct 1995 (Box 55:, Folder 24)
    - Press Clips - Nov 1995 (Box 55:, Folder 25)
    - Press Clips - Dec 1995 (Box 55:, Folder 26)
    - Press Clips - Editorials - Courant (1 of 2) 1995 (Box 55:, Folder 27)
    - Press Clips - Editorials - Courant (2 of 2) 1995 (Box 55:, Folder 28)
    - Press Clips - Elections - Municipal, 1995 (Box 55:, Folder 29)
    - Press Clips - Kennelly Clips 1995 (Box 55:, Folder 30)
    - Press Clips - BBK (1 of 3) 1996, 1995 (Box 55:, Folder 31)
    - Press Clips - BBK (2 of 3) 1996 (Box 55:, Folder 32)
    - Press Clips - BBK (3 of 3) 1996 (Box 55:, Folder 33)
    - Press Clips - Election: Kennelly vs. Webster Brooks, 1996 (Box 55:, Folder 34)
    - Press Clips - Gas Tax, 1996 (Box 55:, Folder 35)
    - Press Clips - 1997, 1996 (Box 55:, Folder 36)
    - Press Clips - Run for Governor 1997 (1 of 2) (Box 55:, Folder 37)
    - Press Clips - Run for Governor 1997 (2 of 2) (Box 55:, Folder 38)
    - Press Clips 1998 (1 of 3) (Box 56:, Folder 1)
    - Press Clips 1998 (2 of 3) (Box 56:, Folder 2)
    - Press Clips 1998 (3 of 3) (Box 56:, Folder 3)
    - Press Clips - Run for Governor 1998 (1 of 2) (Box 56:, Folder 4)
    - Press Clips - Run for Governor 1998 (2 of 2) (Box 56:, Folder 5)
    - Connecticut Newspaper Clippings - August 1998 (Box 56:, Folder 6)
    - Connecticut Newspaper Clippings - September 1998 (1 of 2) (Box 56:, Folder 7)
    - Connecticut Newspaper Clippings - September 1998 (2 of 2) (Box 56:, Folder 8)
    - Connecticut Newspaper Clippings - October 1998 (1 of 2) (Box 56:, Folder 9)
    - Connecticut Newspaper Clippings - October 1998 (2 of 2) (Box 56:, Folder 10)
    - Connecticut Newspaper Clippings - November 1998 (Box 56:, Folder 11)
- Series X: Media, undated
  - VHS Tapes (Box 57-58)
  - VHS Tapes (Box 57-60)
  - Cassette Tapes (Box 60)
  - Slides (Box 61)
  - Photographs (Box 61)